Christmas in Evergreen is a romance, tv movie, drama film directed by Alex Zamm.
Allie, a veterinarian in Evergreen, reluctantly will spend
Christmas with her long-distance boyfriend.
Bound for the airport, she has engine trouble, and Ryan, headed
to Florida with his daughter Zoe, stops to help.
Sure they won’t meet again, they ignore their attraction, and part ways.
At the diner, Zoe wishes on a snow globe, and a storm seems to grant her wish.
Allie Shaw, played by Ashley Williams.
Ryan Bellamy, played by Teddy Sears.
Michelle, played by Holly Robinson Peete.
Carol, played by Barbara Niven.
Zoe, played by Jaeda Lily Miller.
Spencer, played by Marcus Rosner.
An Evergreen Christmas is a 2014 American holiday independent film written by Jeremy Culver and
Morgen Culver and directed by Jeremy Culver as Culver’s first narrative feature.
The film stars Charleene Closshey, Robert Loggia, Naomi Judd, Tyler Ritter, Booboo Stewart, Greer
Grammer and Jake Sandvig and is set in the fictional town of Balsam Falls, Tennessee.
Principal photography began in Charlotte, North Carolina in February 2013.
The film released direct to DVD on November 4, 2014 with premiere
theater screenings in Nashville, TN and Tampa, FL.
The film was available on Netflix for 38 months from
December 20, 2014 until January 21, 2018.
The film is rated PG.
The tone is emotional.